The essential travel guide for a segregated America
The Green Book: Guide to Freedom is a documentary, history,
tv movie film directed by Yoruba Richen.
In 1936, Victor H.
Green (1892-1960) published The Negro Motorist Green Book, a book that was both a travel guide and a survival manual, to help
African-Americans navigate safe those regions of the United States where segregation and Jim Crow laws were disgracefully applied.
Self - Narrator (voice), played by Yoruba Richen.
Green Book Excerpts Narrator (voice), played by Delbert Hunt.
Self - Smithsonian Institute Member, played by Marquette Folley.
Self, played by Karen Allen Baxter.
Self, played by Jennifer Ivey.
Self - Civil Rights Activist, played by Henrie Monteith Treadwel.
Green Book or The Green Book may refer to:
The film explores themes of civil rights, racial
segregation, racism, usa history, jim crow laws.